<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>xamazonian</title><link>https://xamazonian.org/</link><description>Recent content on xamazonian</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 13:50:12 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xamazonian.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Investors</title><link>https://xamazonian.org/posts/investors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 13:50:12 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://xamazonian.org/posts/investors/</guid><description>Organization/Person Name Number of Investments Number of Exits Location Twitter Facebook LinkedIn Primary Job Title Primary Organization Investor Type Investment Stage CB Rank (Investor) Full Description Aaron Greenspan Toronto, Ontario, Canada Twitter Facebook LinkedIn Founder, Owner LEWYS LENS MEDIA 76,247 AARON &amp;#39;Lewy&amp;#39; GREENSPAN is a nationally-published commercial, press and lifestyle photographer, marketer, producer and digital strategist with over five years of unique creative experience working in the Canadian entertainment, business, news, and digital media/advertising industries.</description></item><item><title>Entrepreneurs</title><link>https://xamazonian.org/posts/entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 13:50:05 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://xamazonian.org/posts/entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Full Name Primary Job Title Location Twitter LinkedIn Facebook Schools Attended Biography Aadil Bandukwala Senior Director Of Marketing Bangalore, Karnataka, India Twitter LinkedIn Facebook Aadil is a B2B Marketing Leader with a proven track record of driving measurable growth YoY. He currently is Director Marketing APAC for HackerRank. Previously Aadil was at LinkedIn consulting CHROs on their people strategy. Aadil has also worked at Dell building their social media talent acquisition and employer brand strategy and has extensively evangelised Belong - a Sequoia Capital backed startup across APAC.</description></item><item><title>Companies</title><link>https://xamazonian.org/posts/companies/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 13:49:52 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://xamazonian.org/posts/companies/</guid><description>Organization Name Industries Headquarters Location CB Rank (Organization) Founded Date Funding Status Last Funding Date Last Funding $ Last Funding Type Total Funding $ Founders 415 E-Commerce, Mobile, Venture Capital San Francisco, California, United States 157,286 2014-01-01 Grace Stanat, Owen Van Natta @techvitamin Communities, Information Technology, Internet 1,377,070 John Pollard 10wickets Hardware, Information Technology, Internet, Retail Bengaluru, Karnataka, India 201,359 2010-01-01 Ashesh Nishant 2020 Fund Finance, FinTech Kolkata, West Bengal, India 143,621 2019-09-01 2020-06-01 1500000 Undisclosed 1500000 Steph Mui 2nd Watch Cloud Infrastructure, Enterprise Software, IaaS, Information Technology, Internet, Software, Telecommunications Seattle, Washington, United States 11,309 2010-01-01 M&amp;amp;A 2020-07-02 11650000 Venture - Series Unknown 72850000 Brett Turner, Jeff Aden, Kris Bliesner 33 Buckets Business Development, Water Purification Tempe, Arizona, United States 191,672 2012-01-01 2016-08-23 Non-equity Assistance 17500 Mark Huerta, Paul Strong, Swaroon Sridhar 365hops Adventure Travel, Internet, Mobile, Travel Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India 1,304,247 2014-04-02 Divya Pratap Singh, Kunal Goel, Sachin Goel 3I/O Ventures San Diego, California, United States 672,299 2014-07-01 Brett Turner 500Friends Advertising, E-Commerce, Enterprise Software, Internet, Loyalty Programs, Marketing San Francisco, California, United States 46,865 2009-01-01 M&amp;amp;A 2013-03-12 5000000 Series B 12900000 Bob Tekiela, Hong Hu, Justin Yoshimura 525K Global Solutions Inc.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://xamazonian.org/posts/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 13:49:45 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://xamazonian.org/posts/about/</guid><description>The xamazonian.org community was formed to bring together Amazon alumni and current Amazonians interested in helping ex-Amazon entrepreneurs.
Please join us to access our global community of members and events to help your startup succeed.
Some of our events include regular meetups about startup growth tactics and brainstorming sessions with founders to address their specific challenges. We also have an active slack group where ex-Amazonians can help each other.
xamazonian.org is not an Amazon affiliate.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://xamazonian.org/posts/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 13:49:35 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://xamazonian.org/posts/contact/</guid><description> Email: contact@xamazonian.org</description></item></channel></rss>